Guide to the Comic book collection, about 1984-2004.
Comic book collection
- Titans, The, 1999; 3 (Box 28)
  Artist/Penciler: Justiniano & Drew Johnson
- Titans, The, 1999; 4 (Box 28)
- Titans, The, 1999; 5 (Box 28)
- Titans, The, 1999; 6 (Box 28)
- Titans, The, 1999; 7 (Box 28)
- Titans, The, 1999; 8 (Box 28)
- Titans, The, 1999; 9 (Box 28)
  Artist/Penciler: Ale Garza
- Titans, The, 1999; 10 (Box 28)
- Titans, The, 2000; 11 (Box 28)
- Titans, The, 2000; 12 (Box 28)
- Titans, The, 2000; 13 (Box 28)
  Author: Jay Faerber
  Artist/Penciler: Devin Grayson
- Titans, The, 2000; 14 (Box 28)
  Author: Bryan K. Vaughan & Devin Grayson
  Artist/Penciler: Cully Hammer
- Titans, The, 2000; 15 (Box 28)
- Titans, The, 2000; 16 (Box 28)
- Titans, The, 2000; 17 (Box 28)
  Artist/Penciler: Adam DeKraker
- Titans, The, 2000; 18 (Box 28)
- Titans, The, 2000; 19 (Box 28)
- Titans, The, 2000; 20 (Box 28)
- Titans, The, 2000; 21 (Box 28)
  Artist/Penciler: Paul Pelletier
- Titans, The, 2000; Ann. 1 (Box 28)
  Author: Geoff Johns & Ben Raab
  Artist/Penciler: Justiniano
- Titans/Legion of Super-Heroes: Universe Ablaze, 2000; 1 (Box 28)
  Notes: four issue prestige format mini-series
- Titans/Legion of Super-Heroes: Universe Ablaze, 2000; 2 (Box 28)
- Titans: Secret Files, 1999; 1 (Box 28)
  Notes: multiple writers and artists
- Titans Sell-Out Special, 1992; 1 (Box 28)
- Tokyo Storm Warning, 2003; 1 (Box 28)
  Artist/Penciler: James Raiz
- Tokyo Storm Warning, 2003; 2 (Box 28)
- Tokyo Storm Warning, 2003; 3 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 1999; 1 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 1999; 2 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 1999; 3 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 1999; 4 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 1999; 5 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 2000; 6 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 2000; 7 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 2000; 8 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 2000; 9 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 2000; 10 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 2001; 11 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 2001; 12 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 2001; 13 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 2001; 14 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 2002; 15 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 2002; 16 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong, 2002; 17 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong's Terrific Tales, 2002; 1 (Box 28)
  Artist/Penciler: Paul Rivoche
- Tom Strong's Terrific Tales, 2002; 2 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong's Terrific Tales, 2002; 3 (Box 28)
- Tom Strong's Terrific Tales, 2002; 4 (Box 28)
- Tomb of Dracula, 1974; 25 (Box 28)
  Artist/Penciler: Gene Colan
- Top 10, 1999; 1 (Box 28)
- Top 10, 1999; 2 (Box 28)
- Top 10, 1999; 3 (Box 28)
- Top 10, 1999; 4 (Box 28)
- Top 10, 2000; 5 (Box 28)
- Top 10, 2000; 6 (Box 28)
- Top 10, 2000; 7 (Box 28)
- Top 10, 2000; 8 (Box 28)
- Top 10, 2000; 9 (Box 28)
- Top 10, 2000; 10 (Box 28)
- Top 10, 2001; 11 (Box 28)
- Top 10, 2001; 12 (Box 28)
- Tor, 1993; 1 (Box 28)
  Author: Joe Kubert
  Notes: Cover title: "Joe Kubert's Tor", irregular-size stored on side of box
- Torch of Liberty Special, 1995 (Box 28)
  Artist/Penciler: Kieron Dwyer
- Totems, 2000 (Box 28)
  Artist/Penciler: Duncan Fregredo
- Toxic Gumbo, 1997 (Box 28)
  Author: Lydia Lunch
- Transmetropolitan, 1997; 1 (Box 28)
  Artist/Penciler: Darick Robertson
- Transmetropolitan, 1997; 2 (Box 28)
- Transmetropolitan, 1997; 3 (Box 28)
- Transmetropolitan, 1997; 4 (Box 28)
- Trenchcoat Brigade, 1999; 1 (Box 28)
- Trenchcoat Brigade, 1999; 2 (Box 28)
- Trenchcoat Brigade, 1999; 3 (Box 28)
- Trinity Angels, 1997; 1 (Box 28)
  Author: Kevin Maguire
  Artist/Penciler: Kevin Maguire
  Publisher: Acclaim
- Trinity Angels, 1997; 2 (Box 28)
- Trinity Angels, 1997; 3 (Box 28)
- Trinity Angels, 1997; 4 (Box 28)
- Trinity Angels, 1997; 5 (Box 28)
- Trinity Angels, 1997; 6 (Box 28)
- Trinity Angels, 1998; 7 (Box 28)
- Trinity Angels, 1998; 8 (Box 28)
- Trinity Angels, 1998; 9 (Box 28)
- Trinity Angels, 1998; 10 (Box 28)
- Trinity Angels, 1998; 12 (Box 28)
- Triple X, 1994; 1 (Box 28)
  Author: Pander Brothers
  Notes: seven issue limited series
- Triple X, 1995; 2 (Box 28)
- Triple X, 1995; 3 (Box 28)
- Triple X, 1995; 4 (Box 28)
- Triple X, 1995; 5 (Box 28)
- Triple X, 1995; 6 (Box 28)
- Triple X, 1995; 7 (Box 28)
- Trouble With Girls: Night of the Lizard, 1993; 1 (Box 28)
  Author: Will Jacobs, Gerard Jones
  Notes: "Heavy Hitters" line
- Trouble With Girls: Night of the Lizard, 1993; 2 (Box 28)
- True Crime Comics Special, 1993; 2 (Box 29)
  Author: Jerry Proctor & David Robinson
  Notes: "Apocalypse in Waco"
- True Swamp, 1994; 1 (Box 29)
  Publisher: Alternative Comics
- True Swamp, 1994; 2 (Box 29)
- True Swamp, 1994; 3 (Box 29)
- True Swamp, 1994; 4 (Box 29)
- True Swamp, 1994; 5 (Box 29)
- True Swamp: Stoneground and Hillbound, 2001 (Box 29)
- True Swamp: Underwoods and Overtime, 2000 (Box 29)
- Tug & Buster (v.1), 1995; 1 (Box 29)
  Publisher: Art & Soul
- Tug & Buster (v.1), 1995; 2 (Box 29)
- U.S., 1 (Box 29)
- Ultimate Spider-Man: Free Comic Book Day Edition, 2001; 1 (Box 29)
  Artist/Penciler: Mark Bagley
- Uncanny X-Men, 1966; 28 (Box 29)
  Artist/Penciler: Werner Roth
  Notes: Reprint ca. 1994; Indicia title: X-Men (sorted under Uncanny X-Men)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1969; 54 (Box 29)
  Author: Arnold Drake
  Artist/Penciler: Don Heck
  Notes: Indicia title: X-Men (sorted under Uncanny X-Men)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1969; 55 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1969; 62 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1969; 63 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1980; 137 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1980; 140 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1981; 141 (Box 29)
  Notes: Indicia title: X-Men (sorted under Uncanny X-Men) Days of future past
- Uncanny X-Men, 1981; 142 (Box 29)
  Notes: Days of Future past
- Uncanny X-Men, 1981; 143 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1981; 144 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1981; 145 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1981; 146 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1981; 147 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1981; 148 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1981; 149 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1981; 150 (Box 29)
  Notes: special double sized 150th issue
- Uncanny X-Men, 1981; 151 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1981; 152 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1982; 153 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1982; 154 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1982; 155 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1982; 156 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1982; 157 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1982; 158 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1982; 159 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1982; 160 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1982; 161 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1982; 162 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1982; 163 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1982; 164 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1983; 165 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1983; 166 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1983; 167 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1983; 168 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1983; 169 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1983; 170 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1983; 171 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1983; 172 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1983; 173 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1983; 174 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1983; 175 (Box 29)
  Notes: 20th anniversary issue. 2 copies.
- Uncanny X-Men, 1983; 176 (Box 29)
  Artist/Penciler: John Romita, Jr.
- Uncanny X-Men, 1984; 177 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1984; 178 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1984; 179 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1984; 180 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1984; 181 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1984; 182 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1984; 183 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1984; 184 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1984; 185 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1984; 186 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1984; 187 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1984; 188 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1985; 189 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1985; 190 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1985; 191 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1985; 192 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1985; 193 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1985; 194 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1985; 195 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1985; 196 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1985; 197 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1985; 198 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1985; 199 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1985; 200 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1986; 201 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1986; 202 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1986; 203 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1986; 204 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1986; 205 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1986; 206 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1986; 207 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1986; 208 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1986; 209 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1986; 210 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1986; 211 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1986; 212 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1987; 213 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1987; 214 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1987; 215 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1987; 216 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1987; 217 (Box 29)
  Artist/Penciler: Jackson Guice, Dan Green
- Uncanny X-Men, 1987; 218 (Box 29)
  Artist/Penciler: Mark Sylvestri, Dan Green
- Uncanny X-Men, 1987; 219 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1987; 220 (Box 29)
  Artist/Penciler: Mark Sylvestri
- Uncanny X-Men, 1987; 221 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1987; 222 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1987; 223 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1987; 224 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1988; 225 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1988; 226 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1988; 227 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1988; 228 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1988; 229 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1988; 230 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1988; 231 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1988; 232 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1988; 233 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1988; 234 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1988; 235 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1988; 236 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1989; 237 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1989; 238 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1989; 239 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1989; 240 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1989; 241 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1989; 242 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1989; 243 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1989; 244 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1989; 245 (Box 29)
  Artist/Penciler: Bob Liefeld
- Uncanny X-Men, 1989; 246 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1989; 247 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1989; 248 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1990; 249 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1990; 250 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1990; 251 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1990; 252 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1990; 253 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1990; 254 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1990; 255 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1990; 256 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1990; 257 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1990; 258 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1990; 259 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1990; 260 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1990; 261 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1991; 262 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1991; 263 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1991; 264 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1991; 265 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1991; 266 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1991; 267 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1991; 268 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1991; 269 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1991; 270 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1991; 271 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1991; 272 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1991; 273 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1992; 274 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1992; 275 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1992; 276 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1992; 277 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1992; 278 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1992; 279 (Box 29)
  Artist/Penciler: Andy Kubert
- Uncanny X-Men, 1992; 280 (Box 29)
  Artist/Penciler: Steven Butler
- Uncanny X-Men, 1992; 281 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1992; 282 (Box 29)
  Artist/Penciler: Whilce Portacio
- Uncanny X-Men, 1992; 283 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1992; 284 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1992; 285 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1992; 286 (Box 29)
  Author: Scott Lobdell
- Uncanny X-Men, 1992; 287 (Box 29)
  Author: Jim Lee
- Uncanny X-Men, 1993; 288 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1993; 289 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1993; 290 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1993; 291 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1993; 294 (Box 29)
  Artist/Penciler: Brandon Peterson
- Uncanny X-Men, 1993; 298 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1993; 299 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1993; 300 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1993; 301 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1993; 302 (Box 29)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1993; 414 (Box 30)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1993; 444 (Box 30)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1994; 445 (Box 30)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1994; 446 (Box 30)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1994; 447 (Box 30)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1986; Ann. 10 (Box 30)
  Artist/Penciler: Arthur Adams
- Uncanny X-Men, 1987; Ann. 11 (Box 30)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1988; Ann. 12 (Box 30)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1989; Ann. 13 (Box 30)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1990; Ann. 14 (Box 30)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1991; Ann. 15 (Box 30)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1993; Ann. 17 (Box 30)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1983; Ann. 7 (Box 30)
  Artist/Penciler: Michael Golden
- Uncanny X-Men, 1984; Ann. 8 (Box 30)
- Uncanny X-Men, 1985; Ann. 9 (Box 30)
- Underworld Unleashed, 1991; 1 (Box 30)
- Underworld Unleashed, 1991; 2 (Box 30)
- Underworld Unleashed, 1991; 3 (Box 30)
- Underworld Unleashed: Batman: Devil's Asylum, 1995; 1 (Box 30)
  Artist/Penciler: Brian Stelfreeze
- Unseen Hand, The, 1996; 1 (Box 30)
  Artist/Penciler: Ilya
- Valor, 1993; 7 (Box 30)
  Artist/Penciler: Jeffrey Moore
- Valor, 1994; 22 (Box 30)
- Valor, 1994; 23 (Box 30)
- Vertical, one-shot (Box 30)
- Vertigo Jam, 1993; 1 (Box 30)
  Artist/Penciler: Kevin Lowlan
- Vertigo Pop!: London, 2003; 1 (Box 30)
- Vertigo Pop!: London, 2003; 2 (Box 30)
- Vertigo Pop!: Tokyo, 2002; 1 (Box 30)
  Author: Jonathan Vankin
- Vertigo Pop!: Tokyo, 2002; 2 (Box 30)
- Vertigo Pop!: Tokyo, 2002; 3 (Box 30)
- Vertigo Pop!: Tokyo, 2002; 4 (Box 30)
- Vertigo Rave, 1994; 1 (Box 30)
  Notes: compilation, various artist and writers
- Vertigo Visions: Phantom Stranger, 1993; 1 (Box 30)
- Vertigo Visions: Prez, 1995; 1 (Box 30)
- Vertigo X, 2003; 1 (Box 30)
  Notes: supplement
- Vertigo: Winter's Edge, 1998; 1 (Box 30)
  Notes: Vertigo Holdiay special; compilation, various artist and writers
- Vertigo: Winter's Edge, 1999; 2 (Box 30)
- Vertigo: Winter's Edge, 2000; 3 (Box 30)
- Vigilante (v.1), 1983; 1 (Box 30)
- Vigilante (v.1), 1984; 2 (Box 30)
- Vigilante (v.1), 1984; 3 (Box 30)
- Vigilante (v.1), 1984; 4 (Box 30)
  Artist/Penciler: Don Newton
- Vigilante (v.1), 1984; 5 (Box 30)
- Vigilante (v.1), 1984; 6 (Box 30)
- Vigilante (v.1), 1984; 7 (Box 30)
- Vigilante (v.1), 1984; 8 (Box 30)
- Vigilante (v.1), 1984; 9 (Box 30)
- Vigilante (v.1), 1984; 10 (Box 30)
- Vigilante (v.1), 1984; 11 (Box 30)
- Vigilante (v.1), 1984; 12 (Box 30)
  Artist/Penciler: Gil Kane
- Vigilante (v.1), 1985; 13 (Box 30)
- Vigilante (v.1), 1985; 14 (Box 30)
- Vigilante (v.1), 1985; 15 (Box 30)
  Artist/Penciler: Paris Cullins
- Vigilante (v.1), 1985; 16 (Box 30)
  Artist/Penciler: Alex Saviuk
- Vigilante (v.1), 1985; 17 (Box 30)
  Artist/Penciler: Jim Baikie
- Vigilante (v.1), 1985; 18 (Box 30)
- Vigilante (v.1), 1985; 19 (Box 30)
- Void Indigo, 1984; 1 (Box 30)
  Author: Steve Gerber
  Artist/Penciler: Val Mayerik
- Void Indigo, 1984; 2 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1993; 1 (Box 30)
  Publisher: Pen & Ink
  Notes: Signed inside cover
- Wandering Star, 1993; 2 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1993; 3 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1993; 4 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 5 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 6 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 7 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 8 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 9 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 10 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 11 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 12 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 13 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 14 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 15 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 17 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 18 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 19 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 20 (Box 30)
- Wandering Star, 1994; 21 (Box 30)
- War Dancer, 1993; 1 (Box 30)
  Author: Alan Weiss
  Artist/Penciler: Alan Weiss
- War Dancer, 1993; 2 (Box 30)
- Warriors of Plasm, 1993; 1 (Box 30)
- Warriors of Plasm, 1993; 2 (Box 30)
  Artist/Penciler: David Lapham
- Warriors of Plasm, 1993; 3 (Box 30)
- Warriors of Plasm, 1993; 4 (Box 30)
- Warriors of Plasm, 1993; 5 (Box 30)
- Warriors of Plasm, 1993; 6 (Box 30)
- Warriors of Plasm, 1993; 7 (Box 30)
- Warriors of Plasm, 1993; 8 (Box 30)
- Warriors of Plasm, 1993; 9 (Box 30)
- Warriors of Plasm, 1993; 10 (Box 30)
- We3, 2004; 1 (Box 30)
- We3, 2004; 2 (Box 30)
- We3, 2004; 3 (Box 30)
- Web of Spider-Man, 1984; 1 (Box 30)
  Artist/Penciler: Greg Lo Rocque
- Web of Spider-Man, 1986; Ann. 2 (Box 30)
- West Coast Avengers (v.1), 1984; 1 (Box 30)
- West Coast Avengers (v.1), 1984; 2 (Box 30)
- West Coast Avengers (v.1), 1984; 3 (Box 30)
- West Coast Avengers (v.1), 1984; 4 (Box 30)
- West Coast Avengers (v.2), 1985; 1 (Box 30)
  Notes: Ongoing
- Who's Who, 1985; 1 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Abel - Auron"
- Who's Who, 1985; 2 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Automan - Blackhawk Plane/Island:
- Who's Who, 1985; 3 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Black Lightning-Byth"
- Who's Who, 1985; 4 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Cadre - Chris KL-99"
- Who's Who, 1985; 5 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Chronos - Cyclotron"
- Who's Who, 1985; 7 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Doctor Psycho - Fastback"
- Who's Who, 1985; 8 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Fatal Five - Garguax"
- Who's Who, 1986; 9 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Garn Daanuth - Guardians of the Universe"
- Who's Who, 1986; 10 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Gunner & Sarge - Hyena"
- Who's Who, 1986; 11 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Icicle - Jonni Thunder"
- Who's Who, 1986; 12 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Jonny Double - Kong"
- Who's Who, 1986; 13 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Krona - Losers"
- Who's Who, 1986; 14 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Luthor I - Masters of Disaster"
- Who's Who, 1986; 15 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Matrix-Prime - Mister Tawky-Tawny"
- Who's Who, 1986; 16 (Box 30)
  Notes: "Mr. Terrific - Nightmaster"
- Wild Thing, 1992; 1 (Box 30)
  Author: Simon Jowett
  Artist/Penciler: Duke Mighten
- Wild Thing, 1992; 2 (Box 30)
- Wild Thing, 1992; 3 (Box 30)
- Wild Thing, 1992; 4 (Box 30)
- Witchcraft, 1994; 1 (Box 30)
- Witchcraft, 1994; 2 (Box 30)
- Witchcraft, 1994; 3 (Box 30)
- Witchcraft: La Terreur, 1998; 1 (Box 30)
- Witchcraft: La Terreur, 1998; 2 (Box 30)
- Witchcraft: La Terreur, 1998; 3 (Box 30)
- Witching Hour, 1999; 1 (Box 30)
- Witching Hour, 1999; 2 (Box 30)
- Witching Hour, 1999; 3 (Box 30)
- Wolverine (v.2), 1988; 1 (Box 30)
- Wolverine (v.2), 1988; 2 (Box 30)
- Wolverine (v.2), 1988; 57 (Box 30)
- Wolverine/Gambit: Victims, 1995; 1 (Box 30)
- Wolverine/Gambit: Victims, 1995; 2 (Box 30)
- Wolverine/Gambit: Victims, 1995; 3 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1991; 1 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1991; 2 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1991; 3 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1991; 4 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1992; 5 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1992; 6 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1992; 7 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1992; 8 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1992; 9 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1992; 10 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1992; 13 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1992; 14 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1992; 15 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1992; 16 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1992; 17 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1992; 18 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1993; 19 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1993; 20 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1993; 21 (Box 30)
- Wonder Man, 1993; 22 (Box 30)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1994; 0 (Box 31)
  Artist/Penciler: Mike Deodato, Jr
  Notes: Zero Hour crossover - published after #90
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1992; 69 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1993; 70 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1993; 71 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1993; 72 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1993; 73 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1993; 75 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1994; 82 (Box 31)
  Artist/Penciler: Shawn Atkinson
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1994; 83 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1994; 84 (Box 31)
  Artist/Penciler: Nathan Massengill
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1994; 85 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1994; 86 (Box 31)
  Artist/Penciler: Jeff Parker
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1994; 87 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1994; 88 (Box 31)
  Artist/Penciler: John Ross
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1994; 89 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1994; 90 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1994; 91 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1994; 92 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1995; 93 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1995; 94 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1995; 95 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1995; 96 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1995; 97 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1995; 98 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1995; 99 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1995; 100 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1995; 101 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1995; 102 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1995; 103 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1995; 104 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1996; 105 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1996; 106 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1996; 107 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1996; 108 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1996; 109 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1996; 110 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1996; 111 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1996; 112 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1996; 113 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1996; 114 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1996; 115 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1996; 116 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1997; 117 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1997; 118 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1997; 119 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1997; 120 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1997; 121 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1997; 122 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1997; 123 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1997; 124 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1997; 125 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1997; 126 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1997; 127 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1997; 128 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1997; 129 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1998; 130 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1998; 131 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1998; 132 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1998; 133 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1998; 134 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1998; 135 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1998; 136 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2002; 180 (Box 31)
  Artist/Penciler: Andy Lanning
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2002; 181 (Box 31)
  Artist/Penciler: Gabriel Rearte
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2002; 182 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2002; 183 (Box 31)
  Artist/Penciler: Roy Allan Martinez
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2002; 184 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2002; 185 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2002; 186 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2003; 187 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2003; 188 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2003; 189 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2003; 190 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2003; 191 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2003; 192 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2003; 193 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2003; 194 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2003; 195 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2003; 196 (Box 31)
  Artist/Penciler: Drew Johnson
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2003; 197 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2003; 198 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2004; 199 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2004; 200 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2004; 201 (Box 31)
  Artist/Penciler: Shane Davis
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2004; 202 (Box 31)
  Artist/Penciler: Stephen Sadowski
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2004; 203 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2004; 204 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2004; 205 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2004; 206 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2004; 207 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2004; 208 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2004; 209 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2004; 210 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2005; 211 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2005; 212 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2005; 213 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 2001; 214 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1995; Ann. 4 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1996; Ann. 5 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman (v.2), 1997; Ann. 6 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman Plus, 1997; 1 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman: Donna Troy, 1 (Box 31)
- Wonder Woman: Secret Files, 1998; 1 (Box 31)
- World Below, The, 1999; 1 (Box 31)
- World Below, The, 1999; 2 (Box 31)
- World Below, The, 1999; 3 (Box 31)
- World Below, The, 1999; 4 (Box 31)
- World Below, The: Deeper and Stranger, 1999; 1 (Box 31)
- World Below, The: Deeper and Stranger, 1999; 2 (Box 31)
- World Below, The: Deeper and Stranger, 1999; 3 (Box 31)
- World Below, The: Deeper and Stranger, 1999; 4 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1990; 36 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1990; 37 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1990; 38 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1990; 39 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1990; 40 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1990; 41 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1990; 42 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1990; 43 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1990; 44 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1991; 60 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1991; 61 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1991; 62 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1991; 64 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1991; 68 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1991; 69 (Box 31)
- X-Factor (v.1), 1991; 70 (Box 31)